export default data = [
    {
        question: "Which one of these is Identity theft?",
        options: ["Your private information is stolen and used", 
        "An email, letter or text message from an overseas lottery or sweepstakes company arrives from out of nowhere",
        "Scammers are unscrupulous and take advantage of people who want to donate to a good cause or find an answer to a health problem",
        "None of the above"],
        correct_option: "Your private information is stolen and used"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most common form of payment requested in an impersonation scam?",
        options: ["Credit card payment", "Bank transfer", "PayPal payment", "All of the above"],
        correct_option: "Bank transfer"
    },
    {
        question: "Which one of these do you never reveal on the internet?",
        options: ["Your favorite animal", "Your address", "Your favorite color", "The first letter of your pet fishes name"],
        correct_option: "Your address"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of scam involves tricking someone into revealing confidential information through a text message?",
        options: ["Smishing", "Impersonation", "Phishing", "Vishing"],
        correct_option: "Smishing"
    },
    {
        question: "You receive an email regarding an unauthorized transaction on your credit card and are asked to click on a hyperlink to cancel the transaction. What would you do?",
        options: ["Check if the email and hyperlink are from the credit card issuer. Then, ancel the transaction as instructed.", 
        "Do nothing about it.", "Click on the hyperlink immediately to cancel the transaction.", "Call the credit card issuer for clarification."],
        correct_option: "Call the credit card issuer for clarification."
    },
    {
        question: "Your WhatsApp number is being added to a stock trading chat group. What would you do?",
        options: ["Go with the flow.", "Introduce yourself to the group. ", "Leave and delete the group immediately.", "See what the group members are discussing"],
        correct_option: "Leave and delete the group immediately."
    },
    {
        question: "A friend contacts you on social media asking to borrow RM 8,000 from you for an emergency. What would you do?",
        options: ["Don’t really want to help, but out of friendship, lend half of the requested amount.", "Give a helping hand without hesitation.", "Do nothing about it.", "Call the friend to verify the request."],
        correct_option: "Call the friend to verify the request."
    },
    {
        question: "What type of scam involves tricking someone into revealing confidential information through a phone call?",
        options: ["Smishing", "Impersonation", "Quid Pro Quo", "Vishing"],
        correct_option: "Vishing"
    },
    {
        question: "A hot product is now on sale at 50% off on a social media page. What would you do?",
        options: ["Pay now before it’s too late.", "Share with friends immediately.", "Conduct fact check to see if the seller is credible.", "Click the link given to check it."],
        correct_option: "Conduct fact check to see if the seller is credible."
    },
    {
        question: "In which situation is ok to send your credit card information on the internet.",
        options: ["To your favorite people", "No situation.", "Your banker", "Your parents"],
        correct_option: "No situation."
    },
]